A Guide to the Correspondence of Thomas M. Davis - Board of Supervisors Chairperson, 1988-1994
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence of Thomas M. Davis - Fairfax County (Va.) Board of Supervisors Chairperson, 1988-1994
The Library of Virginia
1170669-1170675 and 1170733-1170740
13.7 cu. ft.
Fairfax County (Va.) Board of Supervisors
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These items came to the Library of Virginia in shipments of court papers from Fairfax County under the accession number 42347.
Biographical Information
Thomas M. Davis was a member of the Fairfax County (Va.) Board of Supervisors as a representative from 1980 to 1990 and as chairperson from 1991-1994.
Scope and Content
Correspondence of Thomas M. Davis - Board of Supervisors Chairperson, 1988-1994, includes correspondence from his time as represenative 1980 to 1990 and as Chairperson from 1991-1994.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically
Index Terms
Persons:
Davis, Thomas M.
Corporate Names:
Fairfax County (Va.) Board of Supervisors
Subjects:
County officials and employees--Virginia--Fairfax County
Geographical Names:
Fairfax County (Va.)--History--20th century.
Genre and Form Terms:
Correspondence--Virginia--Fairfax County; Local government records--Virginia--Fairfax County
Contents List
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1988-1993., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170733)
  Journal; Post; Other; Downsizing (Restriction on Development)1989; Other; Journal; Times; Bonds (Transportation); Bonus (Fairfax Co. Parkway); Bonds-General; The Washington Post; The Washington Times; Assorted; The Northern Va. Sun; The Fairfax Journal; Times Dispatch; Tax Survey; Tax Information Package; Tax & Tom Davis Press
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1988-1993., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170734)
  Development (1989); Budget-County (1988-89); C.O.S.T.-Citizen on Sensible Taxation (1989); Abortion- Journal; Post; Washington Times; Other; Affordable Housing-Journal; Post; Washington Times; Other; B.O.S.-Misc. (1988-89); Assorted Campaign Literature; Assorted Letters and Info.; Bills Passed/1989; General Assembly; Fairfax Co./Republican Committee; Transportation-Trucks Taxes-Business; Transportation-Beltway, Commuter Rail, Port Rail; Federal Gov't, Metro, Misc. Human Services; Local Politics; Lorton Correctional Facility; Media General; Police/Sheriff; Public Safety; School; School-Sex Education; Sports and Stadium; 1988 Taxes; Bonds Transportation; Budget-Federal and State; Child Care; County Spending; Development; Discrimination; EDA (Economics Development Authority); Employment; Environment; Fairfax Co.-Government Center; Gypsy Math; Herrity, Jack; Housing; Environment; Environment-Jet Noise; Dept. of Environment Management-DEM; Fairfax Co. Governmental Center-New Building; File Index; Fire/Rescue; Special Issues; 1990 General Assembly; 1991 General Assembly; Gypsy Moths; Health Dept./Health Issues; Va. House of Delegates; Housing
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1988-1993., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170695)
  Human Services; Lambert, J. Hamilton; Library; Lorton Correction Facility; Lorton Landfill; Misc. Mason District Government Expansion; Moore, Audrey; Parks; Planning Commission; Police/Sheriff; Political Cartoon; Pollution Control; Recycling; Redistricting; Restriction on Developing (Down zoning); Business Taxes; Tax Correction Efforts; Taxes-Local Income Tax; Real Estate/Property Taxes; Taxes- General; School Boundaries/Issues; School Budget
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1988-1993., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170736)
  School Board; School Sex Education; Senior Citizens; Sewage; Smoking Laws; Solid Waste; Schools; Restriction on Developing-Rt. 28; Restriction on Developing-Chesapeake Bay; Restriction on Developing-Ft. Belvoir; Co-Employee; Cigarette Tax (1992); Legislative Letters (response) 1992; Budget; ? (on folder); 1.3m Lease Hrs. (no response 4/92); SACC
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1988-1993., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170737)
  Budget General mailed 3/30/92; SACC (4/92 no response); CIP/Modular Buildings; Teacher Pay; Merit Pay; Budget Hrs.; State of the County (1994); State of the County (1993); Redskin Stadium: CPS-Letter; PTA- Response Letters; FY 1993 Budget (Independent Agencies, Etc.)
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1988-1993., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170738)
  FY1993 Budget Public Safety; FY1993 Budget Human Services; FY1993 Budget General Government; 1993 Budget (Planning and Development); D.E.M.; Transportation-Dulles Toad; Transportation-Metro; Transportation-Metro; Transportation- Northern Va. Transportation Money from Richmond; Child Care; Crime; FCPS state/Equity Issues; Cable (Media General); Budget- County-Pay Cuts; Budget-County.-Cuts/ Services; Budget (Federal and State); Census; Transportation-Commuter Rail Project; Development-Economic Development Authority; Development-Climate for Development; Budget-County-Cuts; Development-Township; Transportation- General
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1988-1993., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170739)
  Utilities; Zoning; Transportation-Fairfax Co. Parkway; Transportation-I-66 Toll; Transportation-Budget/Costs; Audrey Moore; Bonds-General; AIDS; Airport; Transportation-Projects; Transportation-Taxes; Election 1988: Democratic Part 3/8/88; Presidential; Senate; Pari-Mutuel Betting; Community Improvement Bonds
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1988-1993., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170740)
  Human Service; Facilities Bonds; Parks Bonds; School Bonds; Storm Drainage Improvement Bonds; Media List; Presidential Results-Election Results
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1992., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170672)
  January-December
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1992-1994., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170669)
  A-G
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1992-1994., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170670)
  G-O
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1992-1994., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170671)
  P-Z
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1993., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170673)
  January-August; #10000-#24500
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1993-1994., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170674)
  1993 August-1994 June
- Chairperson's Correspondence, 1994-1995., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1170675)
  1994 July-1995 January